<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The PrestaShop architecture on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The PrestaShop architecture on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 15:25:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CQRS</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/cqrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/cqrs/</guid>
      <description>CQRS What is CQRS? CQRS stands for Command Query Responsibility Segregation. In brief, the CQRS pattern suggests to separate &amp;ldquo;write&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;read&amp;rdquo; models, which it refers to as Commands and Queries. In a web application like a CMS, we perform either &amp;ldquo;read&amp;rdquo; operations which return information to the user or &amp;ldquo;write&amp;rdquo; operations which modify the data managed by the application.
Why using CQRS in PrestaShop? During Back Office migration to Symfony, PrestaShop needs a way to access and alter data on the new Symfony pages without multiplying the sources of truth, and without accessing ObjectModel (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain exceptions</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/domain-exceptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/domain-exceptions/</guid>
      <description>Domain exceptions With introduction of domain driven design in PrestaShop, a new way of error handling in the code is seeing the daylight. The code in PrestaShop\PrestaShop\Core\Domain namespace started to utilize domain exceptions.
What is a domain exception A domain exception is an exception, that is thrown in application&amp;rsquo;s domain level, which is specific to that particular domain.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s see how domain exceptions look like in the code. For this example, let&amp;rsquo;s look at Category domain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the &#34;src&#34; folder</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/understanding-src-folder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/development/architecture/understanding-src-folder/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the &amp;ldquo;src&amp;rdquo; folder The main idea when doing the 1.7 release was to use Symfony as a replacement for our own PrestaShop framework.
In &amp;ldquo;src&amp;rdquo; folder you&amp;rsquo;ll find 3 main folders with different purposes:
 Core: the refactored classes or business logic extraction for PrestaShop 1.7; Adapter: the classes that still depends on legacy framework (Context, Dispatcher or constants for instance); PrestaShopBundle: the classes that acts as a glue between PrestaShop classes and Symfony  Core .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>